wapreview.com 2012-05-20

# Privacy Policy for WapReview.com | Wap Review

The privacy of our visitors to _WapReview.com_ is important to us.

At WapReview.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit WapReview.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Personal Information**  
The only personally identifiable information that we collect is the name and email address that you provide when you leave a comment on one of our blog posts or use the contact form to reach us. We use this information only for the purpose of replying to your comment or inquiry. We do not share your email address or name with anyone.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This information is used only for statistical purposes to improve the performance and usability of the site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use cookies to store your personal preferences when you visit our site.

We also use third party advertisements on WapReview.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Interest Based Advertising**  
Google AdSense is used on Wapreview.com.  Adsense serves ads based on the content of the sites you view.  As you browse websites that have partnered with Google or Google sites, such as YouTube, Google may place a cookie in your browser to track the types of pages visited or content that you viewed. Based on this information, Google associates your browser with relevant interest categories and uses these categories to show interest-based ads. For example, if you frequently visit travel websites, Google may show more ads related to travel.  Google will not associate sensitive interest categories with your browser (such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation, health, or sensitive financial categories), and will not use such categories when showing you interest-based ads.

**How do I opt out of interest-based advertising?**  
If you prefer not to receive interest-based advertising, you can click the “Opt out” [button at the top of this page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), or click on the “Opt out” button on the [Google Ads Preferences Manager Page](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Google also offers a number of options to [permanently save your opt-out settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin) in your browser. After you opt out, Google will not collect interest category information and you will not receive interest-based ads.

**Affiliate Links**  
Links to products and services on this site may be affiliate links. The prices you pay are the same or less than if you went directly to the seller's site but WapReview.com gets a small commission on products purchased.
